Lady Lynneburg!
Are you hurt?!
I'm fine.
I am so terribly sorry!
I should have come with you!
There's no point in having an escort
for the trials for the right to the throne.
I'm the one who insisted on that.
You are not at fault, Ines.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you worry.
Lady Lynneburg.
Lord Darken.
Let's return to the castle now.
Lord Rein would like to speak with you.
All right.
I've spoken with Lynne.
Is it true?
Was a Minotaur summoned to the city?
That is a demon who resides in the abyss,
in the deepest layers of the dungeon.
There is no doubt.
In other words, this is someone's doing.
In all likelihood, yes.
The source is thought to be a ring
found on the corpse of a merchant at the scene.
When Oken did his research,
he found the magic stone in the ring
is of a surprisingly high purity.
It is something atypical
that you wouldn't find on the market.
Minotaurs are a threat level A demon.
Wealthy folk can't just buy something
that can trap a creature like that.
According to Oken,
the crest left on the stone
indicates the ring originates from
the Magic Empire of Deridas.
Of course it was Deridas.
He's often provoked us, but...
Right.
Summoning and binding the princess
with a barrier at the same time
shows we must be very careful.
Plus, he isn't even trying
to get rid of the evidence...
The short of it is
not only was the enemy aiming to
assassinate Princess Lynneburg,
but after that...
He was waiting for our country
to initiate a war.
It seemed they wanted nothing more
than to get what is ours.
Our kingdom's resource,
the relics of the Dungeon of the Lost.
Now then, about the man who saved Lynne...
With a single broadsword,
and on top of that in a matter of seconds,
he defeated the Minotaur.
Afterwards, the secret corps followed
his movements but lost sight of him.
"He disappeared before our eyes
like an illusion," or so the report says.
Unbelievable.
Just who is that man?
Noor!
You survived?!
Huh? What happened?
Don't act like you don't know!
Last night, a demon appeared
near the entrance of the dungeon.
It was a monster like nothing
we'd ever seen 'round these parts.
What?!
It was close to the construction site,
and we didn't see your face
'round here after work, so...
I got worried.
I'm sorry.
Last night I was being followed around by
a shady group of people.
I was so tired I went straight home.
Are you serious?
Why's your face all dirty?
Oh...
I finished cleaning out the mud from
the drain this morning before I got here.
In any case, you're real lucky
you didn't bump into that demon.
I used to be an A-rank,
and if I'd come across it
it'd be instant death for me, ya know?
Was it really that awful?
I'm so glad that one was just a cow...
So what happened to that demon?
Well, seems it was taken down by a mystery man.
And in one blow, too.
Wow...
There are some outstanding people
out here in the world.
Here, your payment for yesterday's work.
Thanks.
So, do you still not care
about gettin' yourself a decent job?
A decent job?
I'm already working
as an adventurer, aren't I?
C'mon, Noor.
I keep tellin' you, you can earn
30 percent more without me taking a cut of it.
I've found you.
At long last!
You're the girl from yesterday...
What?!
I know it may be rude,
but I just needed to meet you,
so I found you via
my Long Distance Detection skill.
So then... your job class is thief?
No, my focus is the magician class.
But in addition to that,
I have knowledge of all six skill systems.
That's impressive!
They're all just at a basic level.
But they're so basic it's pretty embarrassing
to be talking to someone like you about it.
You can't possibly mean that.
Hey, is that him?
Can't be...
Um...
We've got an audience here,
so would you mind speaking outside?
Huh?
What did you do?!
Uh, nothing that would get me in trouble.
There shouldn't be too many people out at this time,
and with my Soundproofing and Concealment
skill no one can eavesdrop on us.
Should I go?
Get out there!
So you don't make anymore dumb mistakes!
Not sure what you mean, but okay.
Man, are we sure that guy actually exists?
We can't find anyone
that the secret corps didn't.
Seems like they're searching for someone.
Don't worry, they can't see us.
Please excuse me
for showing up so abruptly.
I shouldn't have demanded you join me outside
while you were speaking with the guildmaster.
Oh no, that's no big deal.
So, what can I help you with?
I wanted to properly thank you.
I truly appreciate you saving my life!
Not only did you save my life,
what you did amounts to saving the lives
of many others in this nation.
That's a bit of a stretch.
Your skills are outstanding.
I may have actually
just interfered with your fight.
That is simply not true!
I can't imagine what would have
become of me if you hadn't rushed in there...
In that case, I accept your thanks.
Personally, I would like to give you
as much of a reward as possible
for your help with the incident.
I want to seriously compensate you
with my deepest gratitude.
Well, your gratitude from earlier
was more than enough.
I truly need nothing more than that.
No, please let me thank you properly.
My father has also asked to meet you
so he can give his thanks.
You've already done more than enough.
I may not look it,
but I am a person of status.
I must give something to the person
who I owe my life to!
I don't need anything.
Th-then is there anything
you're having trouble with?
Nothing at all.
If you need, I can even talk to my father
about some territory that-
I'm sorry, but I really don't need anything.
B-but...
Why are you crying?
This can't happen.
You have an obligation
to accept my gratitude!
I do?
I will not move an inch
until you accept my gratitude!
I will not leave until you train me!
All right, then.
If all I have to do
is meet your father, then I accept.
R-really?!
But there's no need
for anything extravagant.
Okay!
Now then, follow close behind me.
Uh, right now?
Yes.
I don't want people to spot us,
so I'll use Concealment, Detection Occlusion,
and multiple other skills to hide us.
This place is huge.
Is this... your house?
Yes.
I do think this type of structure
isn't very common...
Come in.
Now that I think of it,
I still haven't asked for your name.
Me? I'm Noor.
Lord Noor, I see.
And what's your name?
My apologies!
I completely forgot to introduce myself!
I am Lynneburg Clays.
It's a lengthy name,
so I go by Lynne when I'm adventuring.
I'd appreciate it if you'd call me Lynne.
Man, this is a really spacious house.
She's probably one of those
so-called wealthy people or aristocrats.
So you don't make anymore dumb mistakes!
Is this what he meant?
Perfect.
Let's ask her where my father is.
Welcome home, Lady Lynneburg.
Ines, I'd like to see my father.
He is currently in the audience chambers
speaking with Rein.
Who is that man?
He's my guest.
He's the one who risked his life
to save mine in that attack.
Understood.
I will lead you there.
Is she the family maid?
Looks like it'd be rough for her
to do cleaning and laundry in that outfit.
She seems super wary of me.
What's the deal, Ines?
And why do you have
Lady Lynneburg with you?
This house is kinda dangerous.
And who might this man be?
Gilbert, step aside.
This person is a guest of Lady Lynneburg.
Oh, the Lady's guest, huh?
Then you're the one
we've been speaking about?
You sure don't look like much.
Please stop being rude.
Also, you will accompany us
to the chambers.
The more escorts the better.
Okay. I'll go too.
That damn Deridas...
He doesn't give a damn about
the non-aggression treaty or anything.
His previous request made that quite obvious.
Hand over all the rights to the dungeon.
If I loan you my empire's military power,
it will be beneficial for you too, you know?
I appreciate the offer,
but I'd like to avoid accepting
scummy offers that could lose me my nation.
You'll regret those words!
That may not be
the only looming threat for us.
It's finally time, huh?
Brother!
You're here, Lynne.
Father!
Yes.
That guy is Lynne's dad, huh?
Lynne, that's the Hermit's Cloak!
Are you telling me you went outside?!
I needed to find the person
who saved my life myself, no matter what.
Is that him?
Yes. This person is who rescued me.
Sorry I've come here in this state.
Lynne really wanted to get here in a hurry.
How you're dressed doesn't matter.
Thank you for going to the trouble
of coming here at all.
Just so you know, I'm not an aristocrat
or anything like that.
I don't know the proper etiquette
of places like this,
and I may do something
considered impolite.
Is that all right?
On the contrary, it's much easier
to speak with you if that's the case.
I would like to formally show my gratitude.
Without your actions,
my daughter would be gone from this world.
I truly thank you.
Oh, it was nothing.
And just your words
are thanks enough for me.
All right! Gratitude accepted.
I'm heading to the baths then straight home.
Nonetheless, sending a savior away
without reward is simply impossible.
Huh?
Tell me what you'd like,
whether land or money.
I will present to you
whatever reward I can.
Is there something you desire?
Oh no, I don't want anything like that.
What?
I see...
So you have no need for money nor land...
Well then, how about
the treasures from the dungeon?
Our country possesses
the world's oldest dungeon.
All manners of rarities
have been unearthed from there,
and are stored in the treasure hall.
You can take about half of the items
stowed away there.
F-Father! That's insanely generous...
Thanks, but I don't want all that either.
I really don't need any fancy thank-you gifts.
What you said earlier
is way more than enough thanks.
No need for treasures either, huh?
Then what could...
I can't sneak outta here...
Well then...
What do you think of this?
Is that... a sword?
Yes.
It doesn't look very good at first glance...
Father, what are you doing?
It's fine, Rein.
At this point, it has already become
nothing more than mere decoration.
This is much better
than just letting it lay here unused.
B-but...
No one will even notice if I switch it out
for the replica that was made.
Now then...
It's surprisingly heavy...
This is pretty priceless, isn't it?
If so, I can't take it.
Oh, no, no, I simply
picked it up on a journey,
and was using it because I liked it.
He picked it up?
It's basically a hand-me-down.
You can accept something like that, yes?
Then I graciously accept.
Good.
Well, would you like to give it a swing?
Sure...
Physical Enhancement.
How's this?
It's heavy, but not so much
that I can't swing it.
Well look at that,
you can swing it one-handed, huh?
You sure are a sturdy one!
Then I'll use it.
Also, about my daughter...
If you are all right with it,
will you help toughen her up?
Things are dangerous nowadays.
I'm rather worried about her.
Me, teach Lynne?
Uh, no...
There's nothing I can teach her,
and that's something
she should decide to do herself.
It's not good for parents to interfere
too much with their daughters, you know?
Yes, you are right!
He sure does laugh a lot.
Well, I better head out soon...
All right.
Sorry I kept you here so long.
As Lynne's father,
I want to thank you once again.
The heftiness is great for training, but...
I feel kinda like
I got something very valuable.
Wait a sec, this sword...
It's about the same width
as the drain by Auntie Stella's house!
Yay!
This may do a better job
at getting the mud out of there!
Yay!
I'll try it first thing tomorrow!
Sir.
We must talk.
I'd like a little bit of your time.
Is she mad at me?
First of all, I want you to allow me
to apologize for my rudeness.
My demeanor was not appropriate
for the one who saved Lady Lynneburg's life.
I would very much like your forgiveness.
Ah, I'm not worried about that at all.
It's fine, so lift your head up.
Thank you for accepting my apology.
Our job is to protect the people
of the Clays family from all dangers.
I want you to understand that takes
precedence over the way I treat guests.
Ah, okay...
So you aren't a maid, then.
Now that you mention it,
I have yet to introduce myself.
I am Ines Harness.
I am part of and serve as vice-captain
of the Clays family's warrior corps.
She's so awesome.
And from an early age,
I've been known as "The Divine Shield."
I was appointed to the role
of shield for Lady Lynneburg.
Primarily, I am who must protect her,
even if it costs me my life.
Since you are the honorable person
who saved her life,
it is the same as you
saving my life as well.
I didn't do anything that major...
From here on,
I will help you however I can.
If you need anything, let me know.
The people who live here
sure are excessive.
But I'll go ahead
and accept the sentiment.
If anything ever comes up, I'll ask you.
But, let me warn you...
Lady Lynneburg seems
to have allowed your earlier attitude,
but your speech and behavior while in
audience with the king was unpardonable.
You are not permitted to take on
such a familiar manner as you did.
Should you continue on
like this in the future,
I will no longer be able
to overlook your disrespect.
Refrain from doing so,
especially in front of the retainers.
Okay. Thanks for the warning.
That is the only thing I have to tell you.
And, I'd also like to know
who I am deeply indebted to.
May I have your name, if you don't mind?
I'm Noor.
Noor?
Uh, did I do something wrong again?
No, I'm sorry. It's nothing.
Now then, I'll be taking my leave now.
Sure.
I guess I did make her mad.
Heading home already, Hero?
That's, uh... Gil... Al...
No wait, Har...?
I'm Gilbert.
Join me for a moment.
Uh...
I want you to show me
what you can really do.
I can't go home...
#2: I Parry Rewards